roonlabs.com 2019-05-21

# Roon Labs: Privacy Policy

We are Roon Labs LLC, a company registered in New York, registered at 96 Round Hill Dr, Briarcliff Manor, NY 10510 ("we/our/us"). We respect the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the use of the Internet and any other electronic communications networks by us. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact contact@roonlabs.com. Please read through this Privacy Policy before submitting any of your personal information to us. You do not need to submit any of your personal information when browsing our websites. 

We collect personal information (which means data from which you can be identified, including your name, email address and postal address) from visitors to this website through the use of on-line forms (for example when you register as a member) and from any email that you send to us. Use of personal information We process personal information collected via this website for the purposes of:   
2.1 providing and personalising our services, including customer care, warranty protection and technical or service support;   
2.2 dealing with your inquiries and requests;   
2.3 maintaining information as a reference tool or general resource so that we may improve our products and services for you; and   
2.4 providing you with information about our company, new products and services and/or product upgrades. You may opt out of receiving information about our products and services by selecting the relevant option on our website or by sending us an email at contact@roonlabs.com. 

We may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individuals are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes. 

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. We use cookies to identify you when you visit this website and to keep track of your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile. Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site, carry out transactions and have access to information about their account. Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored on your hard drive. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about how to do this. However, should you decide to disable any cookies we place on your computer you may not be able to use certain services or facilities on the website. However, switching off cookies will restrict your use of our website. Disclosures: We will only disclose personal information to other companies within our group of companies, business partners, government bodies and law enforcement agencies successors in title to our business and suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf. Other websites: Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. Access right: You have a right to access the personal data held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please write to us at 96 Round Hill Dr, Briarcliff Manor, NY 10510. 

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge our processing of personal data in this way. However, we will endeavour to protect all personal information collected through this website in accordance with strict data protection standards. Changes to this Privacy Policy: From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. When we do we will publish the changes on this website. If you do not agree to these changes, please do not continue to use the website. If material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by e-mail or by placing a prominent notice on the website.
